Contatar

22 998714209 (Mobile) thiagosantoscunha@outlook.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/ thiagosantoscunha (LinkedIn) behance.com/thiagodsg (Portfolio)

Principais competências

node

JavaScript

Angular

Languages

Portuguese (Native or Bilingual) English (Limited Working)

Certifications

JavaScript - Object Orientation, design patterns and Regular Expressions with ECMA Script 6 v2015

PHP I

C - leve 1, 2 and 3: advanced features in the language

Logic Programming and Algorithms - JavaScript, Ruby and C Language

Developer's career | Java - PHP - ASP.NET - Python - Ruby and Rails - Wordpress Developer - Machine Learning - JavaScript - Angular - Outros

Honors-Awards
CDIP

Thiago Cunha

Software Developer

Macaé, Rio de Janeiro, Brasil

Resumo

I'm a proactive and responsible front-end developer in web systems based on Wordpress. I seek a highlight to start my career as a Java developer, where is my main focus. I possess strong technical skills aligned with creativity, and I also have great interest in new learnings. I have 12 years of experience in developing successful systems interfaces and contributed to offer revenue to the companies in a highlight directive to put my knowledge into practice.

Experiência

Aimbra

Fullstack Node.js outubro de 2016 - Present

Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

Meu trabalho se resume ao desenvolvimento e engenharia de softwares para clientes no Brasil, Finlândia, Japão e Estados Unidos.

Meu trabalho se inicia desde a análise de requisitos, UML para documentação, design UX/UI, até ao desenvolvimento frontend com ReactJS até ao backend com php e principalmente nodejs.

Corujito

Desenvolvedor de front-end novembro de 2017 - Present

Coritiba

Development of applications using HTML5, CSS and Javascript using the SASS preprocessor on top of a JSP platform, JSF, backend with Java, UX/UI Design with Adobe Illustrator Tools and Adobe XD.

Development of the new platform using Angular Technologies 5 using Microservice models in RESTful. All the architecture of the application I decided to do in a more horizontal model to maintain an abstraction of the world oriented to objects.

Sapiensia Tecnologia Software Developer

agosto de 2018 - outubro de 2018 (3 meses)

Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

I act in the development of frontend applications using Javascript in their ES-Next versions alongside the Angular framework in versions 2 and higher.

Also in parallel, work in the engineering Backend application with Microsoft Technologies, using C# programming languages with Framework .Net Framework and .Net Core.

Oneplace

Senior Webdesigner julho de 2015 - junho de 2016 (1 ano)

Responsible for the front-end development of websites using up-to-date tecnologies based on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP and Bootstrap, all adapted to CMSs Wordpress.

3Grupo

Senior Designer

maio de 2014 - maio de 2016 (2 anos 1 mês)

Macaé, RJ

Responsible for the front-end development of websites using up-to-date tecnologies based on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP and Bootstrap, all adapted to CMSs Wordpress.

Tal Publicidade

Webdesign

janeiro de 2012 - janeiro de 2013 (1 ano 1 mês)

Creation and development from small to big brands, layouts and projects involving the graphic design area, web and desktop systems interfaces and interactive videos.

Appai

Design Gráfico

fevereiro de 2009 - outubro de 2009 (9 meses)

Brand development, increased site traffic, user interface for Web sites and advertising revenue. Development of statistical systems and brand strategy.

Fala Publicidade

Designer gráfico

janeiro de 2003 - fevereiro de 2009 (6 anos 2 meses)

Nova Iguaçu e Região, Brasil

Worked with a file handling system for very high resolutions printers and large file formats. Created artwork, layout, video editing and in the background acted in web development using Adobe Flash and tableless principles.

Formação acadêmica

FSMA - Maria Auxiliadora Salesian School 8° semestre, Computer Engineering · (2015 - 2020)